David Wesseling

+44 (0)7804 204 528

david.wesseling1@gmail.com



https://deign77.github.io



Personal statement

I'm a driven, self-taught developer. About 2 years ago, I discovered I had a passion for programming and since then I've been spending every spare moment learning as much as I can. At present, my primary language is C#. You can view some of my recent projects on my portfolio, link above.

Work Experience

Facilities Assistant [May 2014 - Present]

Bloomsbury Publishing plc [50 Bedford Square, London WCIB 3DP]

In this role, I managed Bloomsbury's extremely busy post room, reception facilities and a number of contractors as well as assisting the Head of Facilities with various tasks at Bloomsbury's head office.

- Management of and regular liaison with (including ITTs) various contractors, suppliers and service providers for multiple UK sites
- General Health & Safety management including first aid and fire safety
- Procuring various office supplies & sundries
- Post room supervision
- Utilities & energy management including ESOS compliance
- Managing a fleet of 40 photocopiers & desktop printers including ordering consumables and maintenance and providing basic tech support
- Minor DIY, repairs & maintenance

Reception Coordinator [March 2013 - January 2014]

Portico (Burges Salmon) [6 New Street Square, New Fetter Lane, EC4A 3BF]

In this position, I was part of a small team responsible for front and back of house services for law firm Burges Salmon. My responsibilities included:

- Meeting room booking and setup
- Event planning and management

- Hospitality and catering
- Liaising with various contractors and service providers including taxis, couriers, catering, office supply, florists, etc.
- Switchboard operation
- Store room & wine cellar management

Supervisor [October 2010 - October 2012]

Baxter-Storey (ITV) [The London Studios LTD, Upper Ground, London SEI 9LT]

The duties were much the same as the previous time I held the position but with more focus and time spent on admin and management.

Supervisor [May 2008 - September 2009]

Baxter-Storey (ITV) [The London Studios LTD, Upper Ground, London SEI 9LT]

- Exceptional customer services
- Store room and stock management
- Internal & external liaising with clients, suppliers, senior management, etc.
- Team management
- Cashier duties

Supervisor [April 2007 - May 2008]

Elior UK (Tesco) [Coppetts Centre, North Circular Road, North Finchley, London N12 0SH]

- Customer Services
- Menu management
- Stock taking and management
- Cashier duties
- Team management and training of new staff

Volunteer Worker [August 2004 - July 2006]

Family Care [Durban, South Africa]

- Organisation of and involvement in entertaining and educational activities for underprivileged children
- Soliciting various companies for donation of goods and/or services

- Distribution of donated goods and services to disadvantaged peoples
- Marketing of educational and self-improvement media

Education

CVA College [2004 - 2006] [Cape Town, South Africa]

UK A level equivalent at A/B average

- English
- Mathematics
- History
- Social Science
- Science & Technology

Skills & Interests

- Reading
- Weight training
- Travelling
- Qualified first aider